A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz, General Administration, Series 5 FA818
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Administration, 1958-1979; 5; 55 Cubic Feet 125 boxes.
  - Political Action Activities - Temporary State Commission to Study the Causes of Campus Unrest, 1969-1972 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Political Action Activities - U of St of NY - St. Education Department Rules and Regulations for Maintenance Public Order, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Political Action Activities - Vietnam Moratorium, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Population Council, 1969-1978 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Postdoctoral Affairs, (Faculty), 1971-1977 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Postdoctoral Studies - Committee - Reprint of, 1970 May 29 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Postdoctoral Studies - Comment on Postdoc. Education - Short Statement, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Postdoctoral Studies Committee - AG draft - Comments on Postdoc. Education, 1970 October 2 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Postdoctoral Studies Committee - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Preliminary Plans, RU, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Prequalification Proposals, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - President's House, 1966-1973 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - RU Press - Accrual Accounting Basis + Fimaco, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - RU Press - Annual Reprints, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - RU Press - Annual Reprints, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - RU Press - Annual Reprints, 1971-1972 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - RU Press - Annual Reprints, 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - RU Press - Annual Reprints, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - RU Press - Annual Reprints, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - RU Press Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - RU Press - budget - Auxiliary Services - Acct. No. 97 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Press and University publications - Budget Note, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - RU Press Calendars, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - RU Editorial Advisory Board, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - RU Press - Eugene Kone - Book on Basic and Applied Science, 1971-1974 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - The Rockefeller University Press: Expense Sheet for yr. ended, 1970 June 30 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - RU Press/Graphic Services, 1973-1974 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University Press: Miscellaneous, 1955-1977 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller University Press: News and Notes, 1969-1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - RU Press - "The Newspaper", 1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - RU Press - Peterson's Guides, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - The Rockefeller University Press: Pre-closing summary, 1969 June 30 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - RU Press - Annual Reports - Report of the President, 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Ru Press - The Review, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Princeton - Annual Librarian Report, for Yr. Ending, 1970 June 30 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Professorships: Named, 1971-1974 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Projected Needs and Requirements, 1972-1974 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Program Development, 1972-1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Proposal - Improvement of Systems and Operations, 1969-1972 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Property Management Committee - File I, 1970-1971 March (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Property Management Committee - File I, 1971 April-June (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Property Management Committee - File II, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Property Management Committee - File II, 1972 January-July (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Property Management Committee - File II, 1972 August-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Proposal to Gulf Oil Foundation by the Rockefeller University (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Proposed additions to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Hall and Caspary Hall, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Proposed New Journal: Philosophy and Public Policy, 1970 April 14 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Proposed New Journal: Philosophy and Public Policy, 1970 October 27 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Proposal to Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Protection of Landmark Buildings - Welfare Island, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Prudential Insurance Development Program, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations (Community Relation), 1972 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations: Mr. H. Rubenstein, etc., 1969-1976 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Regarding Publications - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Quinlan, Robert C., 1974 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Radiation Safety, 1972-1976 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Reading Files, 1969 October; 1 of 4 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1969 October; 2 of 4 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1969 October; 3 of 4 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1969 October; 4 of 4 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1969 November; 1 of 2 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Reading Files, 1969 November; 2 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1969 December (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1970 January; 1 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1970 January; 2 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1970 February; 1 of 2 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1970 February; 2 of 2 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1970 March (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1970 April; 1 of 2 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1970 April (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1970 May (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1970 June (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1970 July (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1970 August; 1 of 2 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1970 August; 2 of 2 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1970 October (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1970 November (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1970 December (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1971 January (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1971 February (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1971 March; 1 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1971 March; 2 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1971 April; 1 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1971 April; 2 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1971 May (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1971 June (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1971 July (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1971 August (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1971 September (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1971 October (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1971 November (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1971 December (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1972 January (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1972 February (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1972 March (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1972 April (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1972 May (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1972 June (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1972 July (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1972 August; 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1972 August; 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1972 September (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1972 November (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1972 December-1973 January (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1973 February (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1973 March (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1973 April (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1973 May-June (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1973 June-August (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1973 September-October (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1973 October-November (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1973 November-December (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1974 January 2-30 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files, 1974 February 1-13 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files, 1974 February 14-28 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files, 1974 March 5-25 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files, 1974 March 26-April 10 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Reading Files, 1974 April 15-30 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Reading Files, 1974 May 6-June 20 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Recombinant DNA, 1976-1978 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Regulations concerning the use of facilities and grounds at the Rockefeller University, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1964-1973 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Biology, 1970-1974 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Report - Detente through Soviet Eyes, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Report of the ERISA Administrator, 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Report - FDR Drive Project, 1971-1973 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Report to Government Agencies, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Requests II, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Residence Halls, 1969-1973 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Restaurant Design Group - Publicity materials, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Resumes, etc. of involved firms, 1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Retirement, 1974-1977 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Retirement Matters, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Retirement Matters, 1965-1971 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Matters, 1972-1976 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Matters, CES Working File, 1965-1972 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Matters, CES Working File, 1968-1973 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Retirement Matters,-Tenured Faculty, 1961-1975 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Plans, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Plans and Related Benefits, 1972-1975 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Revenue Bonds, 1973; 1 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Revenue Bonds, 1973; 2 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Revenue Totals, 1975-1978 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - RFP Draft, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - RJKLIS (Rapid-American Corp.), 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - R. K. Mellon Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1972-1977 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Rogatz/Meyers Associates - Hospital, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt Island Status Report, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Roudebush, Ann, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - RU Council, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - RU Council, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - RU Council, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - RU Council II, 1973 March-May (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - RU Council II, 1973 June-September (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - RU Council III, 1974 January-June (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - RU Council III, 1973 September-December (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - RU Council - Development Program - RU Corp. - Advisory Groups (background), 1971 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Running Working Papers, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Russell Sage Foundation, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Safety Committee, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Safety Manual, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Safety and Security II, 1973-1979 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Safety and Security - Ad Hoc Committee - Writing File, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Safety and Security - CES Working Files, 1972-1976 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Safety and Security (Munroe), 1971 May-1972 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Safety and Security (Munroe), 1970-1971 April (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Saga Food Service - Menus, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Saga - FY 76-77, 1975-1976 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Saga Services - Publicity Materials (candidate for RU Food Service Operation) (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Sadjera, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - The Salk Institute, 1971-1974 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Schall, Albert W., 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Schmitt, Kenneth C., 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Scaife Family Charitable Trusts, 1970-1975 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Schering - Plough, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships, 1974-1977 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Schrafft Food Service - Inventories - File II, 1969-1973 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Schrafft publicity materials (candidate for RU Food Service Operation) (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Science and Public Policy (Lecture Series - Shannon), 1969-1973 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Security Measures, 1969-1971 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Seitz Installation - Announcements, Invitations, Program, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Seitz Installation - Congratulatory Messages A-F, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Seitz Installation - Congratulatory Messages G-K, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Seitz Installation - Congratulatory Messages, L-Q, 1968 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Seitz Installation - Congratulatory Messages, R-Z, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Seitz Installation - Correspondence - Inauguration, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Seitz Installation - General Arrangements, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Seitz Installation - Guest Lists and Replies, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Seitz Installation - Inaugural Address, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Seitz Installation - Thank You Letters, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Requests, 1969-1974 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Service Systems Corporation - Food Service Division, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - 75th Anniversary, 1975-1976 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Shannon, James A., 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Shannon, James A., 1972 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Shannon, James A., 1973 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Shannon - "Some Comments and Proposals", 1970 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Shannon Report, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Siddiqi, Tonia, 1972-1978 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Site Visit Reports, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Site Visits II, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Smith, David O., 1977 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Society of New York Hospital: 200th Anniversary Celebration, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Soils Engineering, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Space Situation: Journals, Office, Order Service, Press Office, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Specialized Food Services, Inc., Publicity Materials, undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Spectroscopy Laboratory, 1965-1976 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Squash Courts, a proposal for more, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Staff Meetings, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Staff Meetings, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Staff Meetings, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Staff Meetings II, 1973-1976 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Staff Meeting - Administrative, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Staff Meeting - Administrative, 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Standard Oil, 1972-1975 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Stark, Dennis Dr., 1975-1978 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - The University of the State of New York, 1965 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - University of the State of New York - General, 1965-1977 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - University of the State of New York, Board of Regents: General, 1970-1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - University of the State of New York, Board of Regents: Fellowships, 1969-1971 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - University of the State of New York, Board of Regents: Scholar Incentive Awards, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Chancellor's Panel on University Purposes - General, 1970-1971; 1 of 2 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - SUNY Chancellor's Panel on University Purposes - Committee on Advancement of Knowledge - General, 1970-1971 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - SUNY Chancellor's Panel on University Purposes - Committee on The Advancement of Knowledge, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - The State Educational Department, 1976-1977; 1 of 2 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - The State Educational Department, 1976-1977; 2 of 2 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - The State Educational Department, 1976-1978 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - University of the State of New York Education Department: General Information, 1970-1975; 1 of 2 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - University of the State of New York Education Department: General Information, 1969-1972; 2 of 2 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - University of the State of New York Education Department: Foreign Area Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - University of the State of New York Education Department: Office of Higher Education Facilities Planning, 1969-1975 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - University of the State of New York Education Department: Questionnaires and Forms, 1963-1974 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - University of the State of New York Education Department: State Aid, 1969-1976 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - SUNY Water Resources, 1970-1971 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Statement of Funds, 1976-1978 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Sternfeld, Ruth, 1970 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Stewart, James T., 1970-1978 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Stouffer Food Services, Diabetic Diet Materials, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Student Representative Committee, 1969-1977 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Student Research Abroad - Funding, 1971-1973 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Study of Professional and Administrative Positions, 1970 July 22 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Study - Returned Questionnaires, A-B, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Study - Returned Questionnaires, C-F, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Study - Returned Questionnaires, G-L, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Study - Returned Questionnaires, M-P, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Study - Returned Questionnaires, R-W, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - SFS-Subscription Fulfillment System, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Summer Fellowships, 1972-1973 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Survey Report - Plans for the Formation of a Uniform Department - Independent of the Purchasing Department, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Survey Report - Renovations and New Equipment Necessary to Modernize and Consolidate, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, 1969; 1 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, 1969; 2 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, 1970; 2 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 1, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 1, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 2, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 2, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 1, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 2, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 1, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 2, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, File 3, 1975 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Sutton Terrace Management, Allocation Guidelines, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Sutton Terrace - Amendment no. 27, 1969-1970 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Sutton Terrace - Bergman, Alfred N., 1970-1975 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Sutton Terrace - CES Writing File, 1974-1975 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Sutton Terrace - Community Service Corp. Real Estate Analysis, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Sutton Terrace - Individual Assignments and Requests, 1969-1972 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, Minutes, 1969 June-1970 June 5 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, Minutes, 1970 June 26-1971 June 7 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, Minutes, 1971 July 8-1972 June 8 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, Minutes, 1972 July 13-1973 June 7 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, Minutes, 1973 July 11-1974 June 6 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Sutton Terrace Management Committee, Minutes, 1974 July 11-1975 June (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Sutton Terrace, McCormack, Thomas J., 1972 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - S-T Rentals Sutton Terrace, 1970-1973 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Syska and Hennessey: Utilities Study, 1970-1972 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Tax Abatement/Exemption: City Block Socony Hall, 1970-1973 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Tax Abatement/Exemption: Sutton Terrace, 1969-1971 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Technical Services - General Information, 1969-1976 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Tenure, 1976-1978 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Tennis Courts, 1969-1972 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Texaco, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Tower Building, Cost Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building and Plaza - Guarenteed Max Price - File 1, 1969 June-December (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guarenteed Max Price - File 1, 1968-1969 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guarenteed Max Price - File 2, 1970 March-December (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guarenteed Max Price - File 2, 1970 January-February (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 3, 1971 July-November (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 3, 1971 April-June (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 3, 1971 January-March (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 4, 1972 September-December (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 4, 1972 June-August (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 4, 1971 December-1972 May (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 4, 1971 November-December (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building Plaza - Guaranteed Max Price - File 5, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building - Extension of Time, 1969-1971 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Tower Building and Plaza - Completion minutes, consenting claim, other papers of continuing importance (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Tower Building, Boiler House, Plaza Structure - Financial Report 1, 1972 March 13 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building, Financial Report 2, 1972 March 13 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building, Financial Report 3, 1972 March 13 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building, Financial Report 4, 1972 March 13 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - General - Tower and Plaza, 1971-1972 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Tower Building - Foundation Work, Report in 1967 of Dinan Associates (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Tower Building - Turner Construction Company, 1968-1972 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Tower Building, Transmittal Letters, 1968-1970 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building, Requisition Letters, 1968-1970 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building, Progress Reports - Fuller Company #6-#13, 1969 March-October (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building, Progress Reports - Fuller Company #14-#18, 1969 November-1970 March (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Tower Building, Progress Reports - Fuller Company #19-#24, 1970 April-September (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Tower Building, Progress Reports - Fuller Company #25-#31, 1970 October-1971 May (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Tower Building - Lab Floors 4,8,13-15, Job#2294-F-Status Report, 1972 April (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building - Lab Floors 4,8,13-15, Job#2294-F-Status Report, 1971 May-August (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building - Lab Floors 4,8,13-15, Job#2294-F-Status Report #l, 1971 July-1972 April (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building - Lab Floors 4,8,13-15, Job#2294-F-Status Report, 1972 April (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Plaza Structure - Progress Reports #l-#6, 1970 June-December (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Plaza Structure - Progress Reports #7-#12, 1971 January-July (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Tower Building - Project Review for Trustees Meeting, 1967 December 12 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Tower Building - Interiors 2, 1970 July-1971 May (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Tower Building - Interiors 1, 1972 June-1973 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Tower Building - Interiors 3, 1968-1970 June (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Tower Building - Motto, Marilynn, 1969-1972 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Tower Building - Population Council, 1969-1972 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Tower Building: Site Improvements, landscaping, etc., 1970-1978 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Traffic Impact Study of the MTA proposed 63 rd Street Subway construction, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Travel, 1965-1977 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1970-1972 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Trust and Estate Gifts - Pooled Income Fund, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - United States Civil Service Commission, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Government/U.S. Foundations General, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - University Directory, 1971-1973 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - University "Governance"-Brewster Speeches, etc., 1969 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Urban Research Inventory - Office of the Mayor, Office of University Relations, N. Y. C., 1971 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Utilities - Con Ed, Water, 1972-1974 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Van Ameringen Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Van Valer, Robert L., 1973 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Voeller, Dr. Bruce, 1971-1972 (Box 123, Folder 9)